Do you think any of the people's critique of your job is valid?
Yeah, it's their opinion.
But not all opinions are valid.
Yeah, I mean, I don't own them all, but they're their opinion,
so they're free to think whatever they want.
That's not the question.
Do you think any of the critiques of your job are valid?
That would assume that I listen to all of them.
I really don't.
It doesn't assume you listen to all of them.
Have you heard any of them that you consider valid?
This is like interviewing Trump.
Jesus.
No, no, no.
I mean, I haven't heard any that I think are not valid,
if that's their perception.
I don't own other people's perceptions of me.
People say what they say about me.
I can't feed into that.
Do I care about what they say?
No.
Or what they say valid, if they believe they're valid.
All right.
Why are we doing another three-hour interview?
God damn.